<entities>
<expansion>

<name>Mists Of Pandaria</name>

<price>100</price>

<date>25.septembrie.2012</date>

<difficulty>medium</difficulty>

<social_net>Facebook,Twitter</social_net>

<multiplayer>YES</multiplayer>

<category>Pandas,Hellscream,Horde,Alliance</category>

<id>1</id>

<description>Mists of Pandaria raised the existing level cap from level 85 to 90. It introduced a new character class, the monk, along with a new playable race, the Pandaren.</description>

<image>../images/mop.jpg</image>

</expansion>
<!--BREAK-->
<expansion>

<name>WoW Vanilla</name>

<price>50</price>

<date>23.septembrie.2004</date>

<difficulty>hard</difficulty>

<social_net>MySpace</social_net>

<multiplayer>YES</multiplayer>

<category>Horde,Alliance</category>

<id>2</id>

<description>Primul expansion este situat într-un univers numit Warcraft, o lume fantastică introdusă de jocul Warcraft: Orcs and Humans în 1994. World of Warcraft este situat în Azeroth, patru ani după evenimentele concluzionate în Warcraft III: The Frozen Throne.</description>

<image>../images/vanilla.jpg</image>

</expansion>
<!--BREAK-->
<expansion>

<name>The Burning Crusade</name>

<price>70</price>

<date>15.ianuarie.2007</date>

<difficulty>medium->hard</difficulty>

<social_net>Facebook</social_net>

<multiplayer>YES</multiplayer>

<category>Blood-Elfs,Horde,Alliance</category>

<id>3</id>

<description>Selling nearly 2.4 million copies on release day alone and making it, at the time, the fastest-selling PC game released at that point. Approximately 3.53 million copies were sold in the first month of release, including 1.9 million in North America, over 100,000 copies in Australasia, and nearly 1.6 million in Europe</description>

<image>../images/tbc.jpg</image>


</expansion>

<!--BREAK-->
<expansion>

<name>Wrath Of The Lich King</name>

<price>80</price>

<date>13.august.2008</date>

<difficulty>easy->medium</difficulty>

<social_net>Facebook</social_net>

<multiplayer>YES</multiplayer>

<category>Arthas,Horde,Alliance</category>

<id>4</id>

<description>he game added a substantial amount of new content into the game world, including the new continent of Northrend, home of the eponymous Lich King and his undead minions. In order to advance through Northrend, players are required to reach at least level 68 and the level cap for the expansion is 80. The first hero class was introduced, the Death Knight, that starts at level 55</description>

<image>../images/wotlk.jpg</image>


</expansion>
<!--BREAK-->
<expansion>

<name>Cataclysm</name>

<price>85</price>

<date>07.decembrie.2010</date>

<difficulty>easy</difficulty>

<social_net>Facebook,Twitter</social_net>

<multiplayer>YES</multiplayer>

<category>Deathwing,Horde,Alliance</category>

<id>4</id>

<description>Shortly after the announcement of the release date, on October 12, 2010, Blizzard implemented patch 4.0.1, which included the overhaul of the game's playing systems.</description>

<image>../images/cataclysm.jpg</image>


</expansion>
<!--BREAK-->
<expansion>

<name>Warlords Of Draenor</name>

<price>120</price>

<date>13.octombrie.2014</date>

<difficulty>easy</difficulty>

<social_net>Twitter,Instagram</social_net>

<multiplayer>NO</multiplayer>

<category>Warlords</category>

<id>5</id>

<description>The expansion raised the existing level cap from 90 to 100 and introduced player-built, upgradeable garrisons.Most of the player models were updated to have more detailed textures, animations and facial expressions, thus increasing the system requirements of the game.</description>

<image>../images/wod.jpg</image>


</expansion>
<!--BREAK-->
<expansion>

<name>Legion</name>

<price>140</price>

<date>30.aprilie.2016</date>

<difficulty>medium</difficulty>

<social_net>Twitter</social_net>

<multiplayer>YES</multiplayer>

<category>Legion</category>

<id>6</id>

<description>The expansion raises the existing level cap from 100 to 110, features artifact weapons for each class's specializations, includes a new area on Azeroth called the Broken Isles and introduces the demon hunter hero class that starts at level 98. It initially included ten 5-man dungeons and two raids.</description>

<image>../images/legion.jpg</image>


</expansion>
<!--BREAK-->
<expansion>

<name>Battle For Azeroth</name>

<price>180</price>

<date>15.august.2018</date>

<difficulty>medium</difficulty>

<social_net>Instagram</social_net>

<multiplayer>NO</multiplayer>

<category>Horde,Alliance</category>

<id>7</id>

<description>In addition to raising the level cap from 110 to 120, the expansion introduces the Kul Tiras and Zandalar continents and four allied races for both the Alliance and the Horde, while also adding dungeons and raids, warfronts, and uncharted islands.</description>

<image>../images/bfa.jpg</image>


</expansion>
<!--BREAK-->


</entities>